Right now I'm the stupid American and
filming an entire spark plug on a
fishing line, but I love this
>> This is traditional fishing in Columbia.
These two guys fish for their meal every
day with hand lines in a tiny little
boat.
>> Like this is what they do. This is how
they eat.
We're in a little town called Taganga.
Beautiful weather. Let's see if we can
go catch some fish.
>> This is how we're rolling right now.
This is like a traditional village that
is modernized but it isn't. I wouldn't
even say that it's modernized because
it's still very traditional fishing
village. Look at that thing. All right.
We have an old spark plug right here
that's going to be used as a weight.
Bringing up the line.
The spark plug weight is my favorite
thing ever.
See. All right.
My first hand line fish ever. That's a
little baby grouper you need to go back
to daycare, lady.
We are pulled up right now by these rock
structures. Get it, people.
My first fish.
He's got to get ate today. Good catch,
homie.
Round two. And I think we're going to
try and harpoon some
This is where we are now. This is the
little fishing shack that we stopped at.
Just building up here.
Go take a look.
Maybe it's a shutter.
And I guess this would be the kitchen. I
would be happy living like this as long
as I had the people I loved around me
and plenty fish.
Jeff and Cin and Ricardo have given me a
harpoon and instructions to go shoot a
fish. I've only been spear fishing one
time in my life in a life jacket, no
real instructions other than don't die
and come back with a fish.
Head butt. I come around the bend and
there was a whole school of these pink
yellow fish and I shot me one in the
boat. I really want to shoot one more.
Got him.
I just got out of the water where I shot
two fish. Man, I could literally do this
all day long. He is starting to clean
the catch right now. We're wrapping up
for the day. This is today's catch. How
long has it been since you've eaten
fish? Seven years. Lime on that guy.
Oh, wow. I missed it. Good? Yes. I'm on
now.
You know, it's fantastic. No fishy
taste. It just tastes like it's good for
you. Now, how does it feel to have
caught your meal? A whole different
level of appreciation. And look,
then we're paying it forward to this
little cat right here. If you've never
been to Colombia, you've got to change
that. This place is a hidden gem.